http://www.performancelights.co.uk/privacy_policy

Your basket is empty
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Privacy Policy
This is the privacy policy of AutoArt Styling Limited, trading as Performance Lights. In this document, "we", "our", or "us" refer to AutoArt Styling Limited, trading as Performance Lights. We are registered in the UK, our company registration number is 06815160. Our registered address is Unit 1 Block B Harriott Drive, WARWICK CV34 6TJ. Introduction This is a notice to inform you of our policy about all information that we record about you. It sets out the conditions under which we may process any information that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. It covers information that could identify you (“personal information”) and information that could not. In the context of the law and this notice, “process” means collect, store, transfer, use or otherwise act on information. We take seriously the protection of your privacy and confidentiality. We understand that all visitors to our website are entitled to know that their personal data will not be used for any purpose unintended by them, and will not accidentally fall into the hands of a third party. We undertake to preserve the confidentiality of all information you provide to us. Our policy complies with UK law accordingly implemented, including that required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). The law requires us to tell you about your rights and our obligations to you as regards the processing and control of your personal data. We do so by requesting that you read the information provided at www.knowyourprivacyrights.org
Except as set out below we do not share, sell, or disclose to any third party any information collected through our website.
The bases on which we process information about you The law requires us to determine under which of six defined bases we process different categories of your personal information, and to notify you of the basis for each category. If a basis on which we process your personal information is no longer relevant then we shall immediately stop processing your data. If the basis changes then if required by law we shall notify you of the change and of any new basis under which we have determined that we can continue to process your information.
1. Information we process because we have a contractual obligation with you When you create an account on our website, buy a product or service from us, or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed between you and us. In order to carry out our obligations under that contract we must process the information you give us. Some of this information may be personal information. We may use it in order to: 1.1 Verify your identity for security purposes; 1.2 Sell products to you; 1.3 Provide you with our services; 1.4 Provide you with suggestions and advice on products, services and how best to use our website. We process this information on the basis that there is a contract between us, or that you have requested we use this information before we enter into a legal contract. Additionally, we may aggregate this information in a general way and use it to provide class information, for example to monitor our performance with respect to a particular service we provide. If we use it for this purpose, you as an individual will not be personally identifiable. We shall continue to process this information until the contract between us ends or is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.
2. Information we process with your consent Through certain actions when otherwise there is no contractual relationship between us, such as when you browse our website or ask us to provide you with more information about our products and services, you provide your consent to us to process information that may be personal information. Wherever possible, we aim to obtain your explicit consent to process this information, for example, by asking you to agree to our use of cookies. Sometimes you might give your consent implicitly, such as when you send us a message by e-mail to which you would reasonably expect us to reply. Except where you have consented to our use of your information for a specific purpose, we do not use your information in any way that would identify you personally. We may aggregate it in a general way and use it to provide class information, for example to monitor the performance of a particular page on our website. We continue to process your information on this basis until you withdraw your consent or it can be reasonably assumed that your consent no longer exists. You may withdraw your consent at any time by instructing us at sales@autoartltd.co.uk. However, if you do so, you may not be able to continue using our website or services.
3. Information we process because we have a legal obligation We are subject to the law like everyone else, and sometimes we are obliged to process your information in order to comply with a statutory obligation. For example, we may be required to give information to legal authorities if they so request or if they have the proper authorisation such as a search warrant or court order. This may include your personal information. 4. What information do we process? 4.1 Information you provide when ordering from us You provide such information when you search, buy, or order via our website. As a result of those actions you may supply us with such information as your name, address, phone numbers and credit card details. 4.2 Information relating to your method of payment Our site uses an online ordering system for customers to purchase products and services. We collect visitors’ contact information (eg. their names, address, telephone number and e-mail address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. Financial information that is collected is used to charge the user for products and services. At the point of payment, you are transferred to a secure page on the website of SagePay or PayPal. That page may be branded to look like a page on our website, but it is not controlled by us. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card processor during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu. We do not hold customer credit card details on our server. 4.3 Information we process automatically Watchstrapworld may collect and analyze the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet and to our website. This is done for tracking purposes to combat fraud, for instance if someone gains access to your personal or financial information, and opens an account or makes purchases in your name. 4.4 Reviews you post on our website Our website allows you to post reviews about the product or service you have purchased with a view to that information being read or used by other people. The review system is administered by a third party, Yotpo, whose privacy policy can be found here: https://www.yotpo.com/privacy-policy/. If you make a purchase from our website, you will automatically receive an email from Yotpo inviting you to leave a review of your purchase experience. We do not specifically use this review information except to allow it to be displayed on our website. We do store it, and we reserve a right to use it in the future in any way we decide. Provided your request is reasonable and there is no legal basis for us to retain it, then at our discretion we may agree to your request to delete your review with any personal information that you have posted. You can also ask not to receive review invitation emails. You can make a request by contacting us at sales@autoartltd.co.uk. 4.5 Messages sent to our support team When you contact us through our website or by e-mail, we collect the data you have given to us in order to respond with the information you require. We record your request and our reply in order to increase the efficiency of our business. We keep personally identifiable information associated with your message such as your name and email address so as to be able to track our communications with you to provide a high quality service.
4.6 Complaints When we receive a complaint, we record all the information you have given to us. We use that information to resolve your complaint. If your complaint reasonably requires us to contact some other person or organisation we may need to provide them with some or all of the information contained in your complaint. We do this as infrequently as possible, but it is a matter for our sole discretion as to whether we do give information, and if we do, what that information is. We may also compile statistics showing information obtained from this source to assess the level of service we provide, but not in a way that could identify you or any other person. 4.7 Information we obtain from third parties Although we do not disclose your personal information to any third party (except as set out in this notice), we sometimes receive data that is indirectly made up from your personal information from third parties whose services we use. No such information is personally identifiable to you. 4.8 Information provided by Cookies Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by your web browser when you visit a website. They allow information gathered on one web page to be stored until it is needed for use on another, allowing a website to provide you with a personalised experience, and the website owner with statistics about how you use the website so that it can be improved. Some cookies may last for a defined period of time, such as one day or until you close your browser. Others last indefinitely. Our website uses third party cookies. They are placed by software that operates on our servers, and by software operated by third parties whose services we use. An example is that we use Google Analytics to measure the performance of our website. We may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes: • To improve the website’s usability; • To analyse your use of our website; • To provide certain interactive functionality, such as remembering your answers to previous questions on a multi-page questionnaire or remembering the contents of your shopping cart. Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies, and to delete ones that have been placed on your computer. If you do not want us to use cookies, you may disable their use in your browser. However, if you do so then please note that you may not be able to use all the features on our website. 4.9 Credit reference information To assist in combating fraud, we share information with credit reference agencies insofar as it relates to clients or customers who instruct their credit card issuer to cancel payment to us without having first provided an acceptable reason to us and given us the opportunity to refund their money.
5. Data may be processed outside the European Union Our websites are hosted in UK. We may also use outsourced services in countries outside the European Union from time to time in other aspects of our business. Accordingly, data obtained within the UK or any other country could be processed outside the European Union. 6. Access to your personal information According to the Data Protection Act, you have the right to free information about your stored data, and also the right to correct, block or delete this data. 6.1 At any time you may review or update personally identifiable information that we hold about you, by signing in to your account on our website; 6.2 To obtain a copy of any information that is not provided on our website you may send us a request at sales@autoartltd.co.uk; 6.3 After receiving the request, we will tell you when we expect to provide you with the information, and whether we require any fee for providing it to you;
6.4 If you have previously given us consent to contact you by any means (for instance by signing up to our newsletter), you may withdraw that consent at any time by contacting us at sales@autoartltd.co.uk.
6.4 If you wish us to remove your personal information from our website, you may contact us at sales@autoartltd.co.uk and ask us to do so. 7. Verification of your identity When we receive any request to access, edit or delete personal information we will first take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is important to safeguard your information. 8. Use of site by children 8.1 We are prohibited from collecting personal information for children under the age of 13. In cases where we have inadvertently collected the personal information of a child, the parent can review this information, choose to have this information deleted from our records, and refuse to permit further collection or use of this information.
8.2 If you are under 18, you may use our website only with consent from a parent or guardian. 9. How to complain 9.1 If you do not agree with our privacy policy or if you have any complaint then you should tell us by email. Our address is sales@autoartltd.co.uk; 9.2 If a dispute is not settled then we ask you to agree to attempt to resolve it by engaging in good faith with us in a process of mediation or arbitration; 9.3 If you are in any way dissatisfied about how we process your personal information, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner's Office. This can be done at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/.
10. Retention period for personal data Except as otherwise mentioned in this privacy notice, we keep your personal information only for as long as required by us: 10.1 To provide you with the services you have requested; 10.2 To comply with any other relevant law, including for the period demanded by our tax authorities; 10.3 To support a claim or defence in court.
11. Compliance with the law Our privacy policy has been compiled so as to comply with the law of every country or legal jurisdiction in which we aim to do business. If you believe it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, please get in touch with us. 12. Review of this privacy policy We may update this privacy notice from time to time as we deem necessary. The terms that apply to you are those posted here on our website on the day you use our website. We advise you to print a copy for your records.
13. Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions If you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over privacy arising therefrom is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including any limitations on damages and arbitration of disputes, and is subject to the Law of England and Wales. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
14. Questions Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu, or you can email us at sales@autoartltd.co.uk.
Customer Service
Terms & Conditions
Payment
Delivery
Warranty & Returns
Privacy Policy
My account
My Account
Performance Lights Unit 1, Block B Harriott Drive, Heathcote Ind Est Warwick WARWICKSHIRE CV34 6TJ United Kingdom
sales@performancelights.co.uk
0843 289 9885
Payment Options
Copyright © 2018 Performance Lights. All Rights Reserved.
Powered by eSeller Solutions
